[
{	
	"content" : "Computer Networking",
	"question" : "A network router joins two _________ together?",
	"a": "Computers",
	"b": "Switches",
	"c": "Networks",
	"d": "Gateway",
	"answer":  "C"
},
{	
	"content" : "Computer Networking",
	"question" : "Ping command works on which protocol?",
	"a": "ICMP",
	"b": "TCP",
	"c": "IP",
	"d": "UDP",
	"answer":  "A"
},
{	
	"content" : "Computer Networking",
	"question" : "What is the port number for HTTP?",
	"a": "25",
	"b": "80",
	"c": "21",
	"d": "65",
	"answer":  "B"
},
{	
	"content" : "Computer Networking",
	"question" : "WHat is the size of an IP address?",
	"a": "64 bit",
	"b": "128 bit",
	"c": "16 bit",
	"d": "32 bit",
	"answer":  "D"
},
{	
	"content" : "Computer Networking",
	"question" : "A network point that provides entrance into another network is called as ___________",
	"a": "Node",
	"b": "Gateway",
	"c": "Switch",
	"d": "Router",
    "answer":  "B"
},
{	
	"content" : "Computer Networking",
	"question" : "TELNET used _________ protocol for data connection",
	"a": "TCP",
	"b": "UDP",
	"c": "IP",
	"d": "DHCP",
	"answer":  "A"
},
{	
	"content" : "Computer Networking",
	"question" : "IPv6 has _______ -bit addresses.",
	"a": "32",
	"b": "64",
	"c": "128",
	"d": "Variable",
	"answer":  "C"
},
{
    "content" : "Computer Networking",
    "question" : "Which of the folowings is not a direct implication of subnet masks in TCP/IP networks?",
    "a": "Reduce network traffic",
    "b": "Increase network security",
    "c": "Assignment of more IP addresses",
    "d": "Better network management",
    "answer":  "C"
},
{
    "content" : "Computer Networking",
    "question" : "Which application below uses the UDP protocol?",
    "a": "DNS",
    "b": "TFTP",
    "c": "RIP",
    "d": "All of the above",
    "answer":  "C"
},
{
    "content" : "Computer Networking",
    "question" : "Which of the following is private IP address?",
    "a": "12.0.0.1",
    "b": "168.172.19.39",
    "c": "172.15.14.36",
    "d": "192.168.24.43",
    "answer":  "D"
}
]
